Serhat Yavuzyigit

Recent Graduate

Ankara, TURKEY

soyavuzyigit@gmail.com

(+90) 506 336 95 24

github.com/serhatyavuzyigit

The motivated student completed the Computer Engineering degree. Gained experience with two long term internships in software development and one long term internship in a research role. Experienced in Agile and Scrum environments. Supports team members with the project, design, and programming needs. Fluent in English and Turkish. Want to contribute to the world to become a better place.



EDUCATION

2016-09 -**Bachelor of Science: Computer Engineering** 2020-12

TOBB University of Economics And Technology - Ankara, TURKEY

- Graduated with 3.07/4.00 GPA
- Courses Taken: Data Structures, Algorithms, Software Engineering, Computer Graphics, Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning, Operating Systems, Database Systems...



WORK EXPERIENCE

2020-09 - Research And Development Intern

2020-12

ESEN, Ankara, TURKEY

- I worked with Research And Development team on Computer Vision and Deep Learning.
- Implemented different Computer Vision algorithms on Matlab and Python
- Gained experience on researching with scientific papers.

2019-09 - Software Engineer Intern

2019-12

AYESAS, Ankara, TURKEY

- Worked with a software engineering project team.
- Gained experience with avionics software development and Microsoft Visual Studio environment.
- Developed a tool using C++ and QT.

2019-01 -**Software Engineer Intern** 2019-04

SimBT, Ankara, TURKEY

- Worked with a scrum team in defence industry software engineering project.
- Contributed to project with solving bugfixes, making improvements and refactoring the code.
- Gained experience with Java, JavaFX, Git and Maven.



- Software Development
- Algorithms and Data Structures
- Java, C, C++, Python, JavaScript, OpenGL Programming



- Machine Learning
- Data Structures and Algorithms
- Android / iOS Development
- Science
- Sports



PROJECTS

 You can see my programming projects and code snippets on my GitHub page